here are those six topic areas again
这又是这六个主题领域
I am describing activity is the fifth one in this series of lessons
我描述的活动是本系列课程的第五部分
let's look at this topic now
让我们现在来看这个话题
when your asked to describe an activity I think this is quite an easy topic
当您要求描述活动时，我认为这是一个很简单的话题
but we still have to prepare some good vocabulary for it so that we're ready
但是我们仍然需要为此准备一些好的词汇，以便我们做好准备
you'll be asked
你会被问到
on the task card
在任务卡上
to describe
来描述
what where
什么哪里
who and why usually
通常是谁和为什么
what the activity is
活动是什么
where you do it who you do it with why you like it that kind of thing
你在哪里做，和谁一起做，为什么喜欢它
let's look at some example questions that i've seen
我们来看一些我看过的示例问题
in the official illes materials or in real tests
在官方illes材料或实际测试中
one activity that you could be asked to describe of course is a hobby
您可能被要求描述的一项活动当然是一种爱好
a sport
一种运动
something healthy that you do
做些健康的事
and something new that you have done recently
还有你最近做的新事
my suggestion as usual is to prepare vocabulary themes
我通常的建议是准备词汇主题
to take an easy word
说一个简单的话
and then build some really good vocabulary around it and that's what we're going to do
然后围绕它建立一些非常好的词汇，这就是我们要做的